<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<!-- This file is part of the re-motion Core Framework (www.re-motion.org)
 ! Copyright (c) rubicon IT GmbH, www.rubicon.eu
 ! 
 ! The re-motion Core Framework is free software; you can redistribute it 
 ! and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU Lesser General Public License 
 ! as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2.1 of the 
 ! License, or (at your option) any later version.
 ! 
 ! re-motion is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, 
 ! but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of 
 ! MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the 
 ! GNU Lesser General Public License for more details.
 ! 
 ! You should have received a copy of the GNU Lesser General Public License
 ! along with re-motion; if not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses.
-->
<TypesafeInvoker>
  <Class>
    <remarks>
      <para>
        In order to call a specific method or constructor using reflection, you often have to provide a list of argument types. However, manually
        specifying this list is tedious and error-prone. Consider the following example (assuming Window is derived from Control):
      </para><code>
<![CDATA[
void SampleMethod (int i, string s, object o);
void SampleMethod (int i, string s, Control c);
void SampleMethod (int i, string s, Window w);
 
int integer; string str; Control ctrl;
MethodInfo method = type.GetMethod ("SampleMethod", new Type[] { typeof(int), typeof(string), typeof(Control) });
method.Invoke (new object[] { integer, str, ctrl });
]]>
      </code><para>
        A common workaround is to accept an array of values and determine the types from those values via GetType(), like Activator.CreateInstance()
        does. In fact, this is just what IFuncInvoker.Invoke (object[]) does.
      </para><para>
        The problem with this type of overload is that the types are determined at runtime. In the previous example, different methods would be called
        depending on the runtime value of ctrl. If ctrl is null, the first overload would be called (because the runtime type of null can only be resolved
        to object). If ctrl is a Window, the third overload would be called. In any other case, the second overload would be called. This is usually
        not what programmers would expect.
      </para><para>
        If ctrl is of a type for which no explicit overload exists, the overload for type object is called (overload no. 1). If there is no overload for
        the object type, the call usually results in an exception.
      </para><para>
        InvokeWith uses generic methods to pass the compile-time type information to the invoke method.
      </para><code>
invoker.CallMethod (obj, "SampleMethod").With (integer, str, ctrl);
      </code><para>
        would always call the second overload of SampleMethod, because the variable ctrl has the static type Control. The previous line is the same as
        the more explicit
      </para><code>
invoker.CallMethod (obj, "SampleMethod").With&lt;int,string,Control&gt; (integer, str, ctrl);
      </code><para>
        The following table gives an overview on which overloads would be selected given a value of ctrl:
      </para><code>
<![CDATA[
Value of ctrl         Dynamic (get types from object[])   IFuncInvoker.With<A1,A2,A3>
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
null                  SampleMethod (int, string, object)  SampleMethod (int, string, Control)
new Control()         SampleMethod (int, string, Control) SampleMethod (int, string, Control)
new Window()          SampleMethod (int, string, Window)  SampleMethod (int, string, Control)
new SpecialControl()  no match                            SampleMethod (int, string, Control)
]]>
      </code><para>
        To use InvokeWith, create a method that returns an instance of a subclass of InvokeWith. Pass your method's parameters to this instance and
        do the actual processing in your override of Invoke(). Refer to <see ref="TypesafeActivator"/> for an example implementation of a method
        using InvokeWith.
      </para>
    </remarks>
    <typeparam name="T"> Return type of YourMethod(...).With(...)</typeparam>
  </Class>  
</TypesafeInvoker>
