<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- This file is part of the re-motion Core Framework (www.re-motion.org)
 ! Copyright (c) rubicon IT GmbH, www.rubicon.eu
 ! 
 ! The re-motion Core Framework is free software; you can redistribute it 
 ! and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU Lesser General Public License 
 ! as published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2.1 of the 
 ! License, or (at your option) any later version.
 ! 
 ! re-motion is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, 
 ! but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of 
 ! MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the 
 ! GNU Lesser General Public License for more details.
 ! 
 ! You should have received a copy of the GNU Lesser General Public License
 ! along with re-motion; if not, see http://www.gnu.org/licenses.
-->
<WxePageStep>
  <Class>
    <remarks>   
      <para>
        A <b>WxePageStep</b> is used to incorporatre user interaction into a <see cref="WxeStepList"/> or 
        <see cref="WxeFunction"/> in the form of an <b>ASPX Page</b>  that implents the <see cref="IWxePage"/>
        interface.
      </para><para>
        Unlike steps without user interaction, the <b>WxePageStep</b> must transfer control to the <b>ASP.NET</b>
        infrastructure to display the page. Once the page has been rendered, the execution of the thread stops
        unitl it is resumed with a new post back request from the client. During the post back, the execution
        engine offers the following means of directing the control flow.
      </para>
      <list type="table">
        <listheader>
          <term>
            Server side event handler action
          </term>
          <description>
            Resulting exection engine behavior
          </description>
        </listheader>
        <item>
          <term>
            The event is handled by the page and results in the reposting of the page.
          </term>
          <description>
            The execution engine does not change the behavior of the <b>ASP.NET</b> control flow.
          </description>
        </item>
        <item>
          <term>
            The event handler invokes the <see cref="IWxePage.ExecuteNextStep"/> method. 
          </term>
          <description>
            The page's <b>PreRender</b> and <b>Render</b> phases will not execute and the execution is transfered
            back to the executing <b>WxePageStep</b>, which will then end.
          </description>
        </item>
        <item>
          <term>
            The event handler throws an exception. 
          </term>
          <description>
            The execution path will immedeatly leave the page and the exception will be passed through the 
            hierarchy of steps until it is caught by a <see cref="Obsolete.WxeTryCatch"/> block or by a 
            <see cref="WxeFunction"/> where the exception type has been registered for catching. Please refer
            to the <see cref="WxeFunction"/>'s documentation for details on working with exceptions.
          </description>
        </item>
        <item>
          <term>
            The event handler invokes a sub-function. 
          </term>
          <description>
            The <b>WxePageStep</b> will back-up the page's post back data and transfer execution to the sub-function.
            After the execution has completed, the original post back data will be restored and the page's execution
            will restart with the post back cycle that originally caused the sub-function to be invoked. Use the
            <see cref="IWxePage.IsReturningPostBack"/> flag to determine whether the current post back cycle has been
            caused by a <b>repost</b>.
          </description>
        </item>
      </list>
    </remarks>
    <seealso cref="IWxePage"/>
    <example>
      An example where the 3rd step of the <see cref="WxeFunction"/> <b> MyFunction</b> is a <b>WxePageStep</b>
      dislaying a the ASPX page <c>MyWebForm.aspx</c>.
      <code escaped="true" lang="C#">
public class MyFunction: WxeFunction
{
  ...
  // Step2
  WxeStep Step3 = new WxePageStep ("MyWebForm.aspx");
  // Step4
  ...
}
      </code>    
    </example>
  </Class>
  <Ctor>
    <param name="page">
      The URL of the page to be displayed, relative to the application root. Must not be <see langword="null"/>
      or emtpy.
    </param>
    <param name="pageref"> 
      A <see cref="WxeVariableReference"/> pointing to the URL of the page to be displayed. The URL is relative 
      to the application root. Must not be <see langword="null"/>.
    </param>
    <param name="resourceAssembly"> 
      The (optional) <see cref="Assembly"/> containing the page.
    </param>
  </Ctor>
  <Execute>
    <param name="context"> 
      The <see cref="WxeContext"/> containing the information about the execution. Must not be <see langword="null"/>. 
    </param>
    <remarks> 
      <para>
        While the current <see cref="WxePageStep"/> executes, this method will be invoked during each post back. 
        It will then transfer control to the <see cref="WxePageStep"/>'s page. In order to end the execution of 
        the step, it is necessary to invoke the <see cref="IWxePage.ExecuteNextStep"/> method from inside the page.
        This will cause a <see cref="WxeExecuteNextStepException"/> to be thrown, which is then caught, resulting 
        in the completion of the current step. Other exceptions will also end the execution of the step, 
        but will be passed on by rethrowing the exception.
      </para><para>
        During the execution of a sub-function, the <see cref="WxePageStep"/> will transfer control to the 
        sub-function and resume execution after the function has returned. The completed sub-function will then 
        be available via the <see cref="ReturningFunction"/> property 
        for the remainder or the current post back cycle.
        <note>
          The current <see cref="WxePageStep"/>'s <b>Execute</b> method will still be invoked during each post back, 
          but execution will be transfered to the executing sub-function without interaction in the current step.
        </note>
      </para>
    </remarks>
  </Execute>
  <ExecuteFunction>
    <param name="page"> 
      The <see cref="IWxePage"/> being executed. Must not be <see langword="null"/>. 
    </param>
    <param name="function"> 
      The <see cref="WxeFunction"/> to be executed. Must not be <see langword="null"/>. 
    </param>
    <param name="permaUrlOptions"> 
      The <see cref="WxePermaUrlOptions"/> used for executing the function using a permanent URL.      
    </param>
    <remarks>
      Note that if you call this method from a postback event handler, the postback event will be raised again 
      when the user returns to this page. You can either manually check whether the event was re-posted using 
      <see cref="IWxePage.IsReturningPostBack"/> or suppress the re-post by calling 
      <see cref="ExecuteFunctionNoRepost"/>.
    </remarks>
  </ExecuteFunction>
  <ExecutingStep>
    <value> 
      Either the current step or the <see cref="WxeStepList.ExecutingStep"/> of the <see cref="WxeFunction"/> 
      invoked by <see cref="ExecuteFunction"/>.
    </value>
  </ExecutingStep>
  <PageToken>
    <value> 
      A value that uniquely identifies a <see cref="WxePageStep"/> while it is executing. 
    </value>
    <remarks> 
      The page token remains valid until the user leaves the page, e.g. by invoking 
      <see cref="IWxePage.ExecuteNextStep"/>.
    </remarks>
  </PageToken>
</WxePageStep>